<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<sst xmlns="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/spreadsheetml/2006/main" count="237" uniqueCount="174"><si><t>Info</t></si><si><t>GIS Pre-Processing</t></si><si><t>Final POD List</t></si><si><t>QAQC Review</t></si><si><t>NA Reports</t></si><si><t>POD Sub-Basin Assignment</t></si><si><t>INDEX</t></si><si><t>NAME</t></si><si><t>ID</t></si><si><t>WATERSHED_BOUNDARY_DATABASE_PATH</t></si><si><t>WATERSHED_BOUNDARY_LAYER_NAME</t></si><si><t>IS_SHAREPOINT_PATH_WATERSHED_BOUNDARY</t></si><si><t>WATERSHED_COLUMN_SEARCH_STRING</t></si><si><t>SOURCE_NAME_COLUMN_SEARCH_STRING</t></si><si><t>TRIB_DESC_COLUMN_SEARCH_STRING</t></si><si><t>WATERSHED_EXIT_POINT_INDEX</t></si><si><t>GIS_PREPROCESSING_SPREADSHEET_PATH</t></si><si><t>GIS_PREPROCESSING_WORKSHEET_NAME</t></si><si><t>IS_SHAREPOINT_PATH_GIS_PREPROCESSING_SPREADSHEET</t></si><si><t>EWRIMS_REPORTS_FOLDER_PATH</t></si><si><t>POD_APPLICATION_NUMBER_SPREADSHEET_PATH</t></si><si><t>POD_APPLICATION_NUMBER_WORKSHEET_NAME</t></si><si><t>IS_SHAREPOINT_PATH_POD_APPLICATION_NUMBER_SPREADSHEET</t></si><si><t>QAQC_UNIT_CONVERSION_ERRORS_SPREADSHEET_PATH</t></si><si><t>QAQC_UNIT_CONVERSION_ERRORS_WORKSHEET_NAME</t></si><si><t>IS_SHAREPOINT_PATH_QAQC_UNIT_CONVERSION_ERRORS_SPREADSHEET</t></si><si><t>QAQC_MEASUREMENT_VALUES_SPREADSHEET_PATH</t></si><si><t>QAQC_MEASUREMENT_VALUES_SPREADSHEET_WORKSHEET_NAME</t></si><si><t>IS_SHAREPOINT_PATH_QAQC_MEASUREMENT_VALUES</t></si><si><t>QAQC_MEDIAN_BASED_UNIT_CONVERSION_ERRORS_SPREADSHEET_PATH</t></si><si><t>QAQC_MEDIAN_BASED_UNIT_CONVERSION_ERRORS_WORKSHEET_NAME</t></si><si><t>IS_SHAREPOINT_PATH_QAQC_MEDIAN_BASED_UNIT_CONVERSION_ERRORS_SPREADSHEET</t></si><si><t>QAQC_DUPLICATE_REPORTING_SPREADSHEET_PATH</t></si><si><t>QAQC_DUPLICATE_REPORTING_WORKSHEET_NAME</t></si><si><t>IS_SHAREPOINT_PATH_QAQC_DUPLICATE_REPORTING_SPREADSHEET</t></si><si><t>NA_REPORTS_SPREADSHEET_PATH</t></si><si><t>NA_REPORTS_WORKSHEET_NAME</t></si><si><t>IS_SHAREPOINT_PATH_NA_REPORTS_SPREADSHEET</t></si><si><t>POD_COORDINATES_SPREADSHEET_PATH</t></si><si><t>POD_COORDINATES_WORKSHEET_NAME</t></si><si><t>IS_SHAREPOINT_PATH_POD_COORDINATES_SPREADSHEET</t></si><si><t>POD_COORDINATES_REFERENCE_SYSTEM</t></si><si><t>SUBBASIN_POLYGONS_DATABASE_PATH</t></si><si><t>SUBBASIN_POLYGONS_LAYER_NAME</t></si><si><t>IS_SHAREPOINT_PATH_SUBBASIN_POLYGONS</t></si><si><t>SUBBASIN_FIELD_ID_NAMES</t></si><si><t>CONNECTIVITY_MATRIX_SPREADSHEET_PATH</t></si><si><t>CONNECTIVITY_MATRIX_WORKSHEET_NAME</t></si><si><t>IS_SHAREPOINT_PATH_CONNECTIVITY_MATRIX_SPREADSHEET</t></si><si><t>SUBBASIN_MANUAL_ASSIGNMENT_SPREADSHEET_PATH</t></si><si><t>SUBBASIN_MANUAL_ASSIGNMENT_WORKSHEET_NAME</t></si><si><t>IS_SHAREPOINT_PATH_SUBBASIN_MANUAL_ASSIGNMENT</t></si><si><t>SUBBASIN_ASSIGNMENT_SPREADSHEET_PATH</t></si><si><t>SUBBASIN_ASSIGNMENT_WORKSHEET_NAME</t></si><si><t>IS_SHAREPOINT_PATH_SUBBASIN_ASSIGNMENT_SPREADSHEET</t></si><si><t>Russian River</t></si><si><t>RR</t></si><si><t>RR_NHD_1801_HUC8</t></si><si><t>Russian</t></si><si><t>RR_pod_points_Merge_filtered_PA</t></si><si><t>Corrected Data</t></si><si><t>Data</t></si><si><t>Filtered Data</t></si><si><t>Sheet1</t></si><si><t>NAD83</t></si><si><t>InputData/DWRAT_ForImportIntoPortal.gdb</t></si><si><t>RR_Basins_UpprAndLwr</t></si><si><t>Basin_ID; Basin_Num; Grouping</t></si><si><t>Missing_MainStem_GIS</t></si><si><t>Navarro River</t></si><si><t>NV</t></si><si><t>WBD_HU10_Navarro</t></si><si><t>Navarro</t></si><si><t>R_Review</t></si><si><t>Final_List</t></si><si><t>COLUMN_NAME</t></si><si><t>DEFINITION</t></si><si><t>DESCRIPTION</t></si><si><t>The watershed's row number</t></si><si><t>Automatically populated. This number corresponds to the row index that should be used when selecting a watershed in the demand scripts.</t></si><si><t>The name of the watershed</t></si><si><t>.</t></si><si><t>A short unique string for each watershed</t></si><si><t>The demand scripts append this string to the start of all output filenames to distinguish between different watersheds' files.</t></si><si><t>Path to the GIS file that contains the watershed boundary layer</t></si><si><t>The GIS Pre-Processing demand scripts require a boundary layer for the watershed. It should be a single polygon.</t></si><si><t>The watershed boundary layer's name</t></si><si><t>If "WATERSHED_BOUNDARY_DATABASE_PATH" leads to a geodatabase or similar GIS structure, specify the watershed boundary's layer name here. Otherwise, leave it blank.</t></si><si><t>Is "WATERSHED_BOUNDARY_DATABASE_PATH" a SharePoint path?</t></si><si><t>Either "TRUE" or "FALSE". If "TRUE", the path should be a SharePoint path compatible with the demand script function "makeSharePointPath" (see "Shared_Functions.R"). Otherwise, the filepath should be a relative path that is compatible with the Demand R project's working directory.</t></si><si><t>Search the eWRIMS "WATERSHED" column for entries that contain this text</t></si><si><r><t xml:space="preserve">Using this string of text, "GIS_Preprocessing.R" checks the "WATERSHED" column of PODs for mentions of this string. The search is </t></r><r><rPr><b/><sz val="11"/><rFont val="Aptos Narrow"/><family val="2"/><scheme val="minor"/></rPr><t>not</t></r><r><rPr><sz val="11"/><rFont val="Aptos Narrow"/><family val="2"/><scheme val="minor"/></rPr><t xml:space="preserve"> case-sensitive. (These strings are technically regular expressions.)</t></r></si><si><t>Search the eWRIMS "SOURCE_NAME" column for entries that contain this text</t></si><si><r><t xml:space="preserve">Using this string of text, "GIS_Preprocessing.R" checks the "SOURCE_NAME" column of PODs for mentions of this string. The search is </t></r><r><rPr><b/><sz val="11"/><rFont val="Aptos Narrow"/><family val="2"/><scheme val="minor"/></rPr><t>not</t></r><r><rPr><sz val="11"/><rFont val="Aptos Narrow"/><family val="2"/><scheme val="minor"/></rPr><t xml:space="preserve"> case-sensitive. (These strings are technically regular expressions.)</t></r></si><si><t>Search the eWRIMS "TRIB_DESC" column for entries that contain this text</t></si><si><r><t xml:space="preserve">Using this string of text, "GIS_Preprocessing.R" checks the "TRIB_DESC" column of PODs for mentions of this string. The search is </t></r><r><rPr><b/><sz val="11"/><rFont val="Aptos Narrow"/><family val="2"/><scheme val="minor"/></rPr><t>not</t></r><r><rPr><sz val="11"/><rFont val="Aptos Narrow"/><family val="2"/><scheme val="minor"/></rPr><t xml:space="preserve"> case-sensitive. (These strings are technically regular expressions.)</t></r></si><si><t>The index number of the R variable "wsPoint" that corresponds to the exit point of the watershed boundary</t></si><si><t>Path to the manually reviewed GIS Pre-Processing spreadsheet</t></si><si><t>To use "POD_StreamStats_Analysis.R", the "R_Review" sheet of the GIS Pre-Processing spreadsheet must be filled out. This path should lead to that file.</t></si><si><t>Name of the R-compatible review worksheet in the GIS Pre-Processing spreadsheet</t></si><si><t>Unless the worksheet names were modified, this should be "R_Review".</t></si><si><t>Is "GIS_PREPROCESSING_SPREADSHEET_PATH" a SharePoint path?</t></si><si><t>Path to the SharePoint folder where you will be saving all of your watershed-specific ewrims REPORTS</t></si><si><t>Required for ewrims_Document_Bulk_Downloader.R script to download all the ewrims reports for the watershed to the correct SharePoint location.</t></si><si><t>Path to the final list of PODs located in the watershed</t></si><si><t>After the GIS Pre-Processing steps have been completed, there should be a final list of PODs that are located in the watershed. That list should be stored in a spreadsheet with "APPLICATION_NUMBER" present as one of the columns. The path to that spreadsheet should be input here.</t></si><si><t>Name of the worksheet in the POD spreadsheet that contains the finalized list of PODs</t></si><si><t>The name of the worksheet in the POD spreadsheet that contains the final list of PODs (with "APPLICATION_NUMBER" as one of the columns)</t></si><si><t>Is "POD_APPLICATION_NUMBER_SPREADSHEET_PATH" a SharePoint path?</t></si><si><t>Path to the manually reviewed Unit Conversion Errors spreadsheet</t></si><si><t>Leave this blank if the manual review has not yet been completed. Otherwise, input a path to the manually reviewed QAQC spreadsheet here. (This spreadsheet should be the file that was output by "Expected_Demand.R")</t></si><si><t>Name of the review worksheet in the Unit Conversion Errors spreadsheet</t></si><si><t>The name of the worksheet in the Unit Conversion Errors spreadsheet that contains the manual review table</t></si><si><t>Is "QAQC_UNIT_CONVERSION_ERRORS_SPREADSHEET_PATH" a SharePoint path?</t></si><si><t>Path to the spreadsheet that contains values from rights' measurement files</t></si><si><t>For some water rights, the chosen correction might be replacing the reported data with the values present in their measurement spreadsheets. In that case, those measurement spreadsheet values should all be compiled into one spreadsheet, and its path should be specified here.</t></si><si><t>Name of the worksheet in the Measurement Values spreadsheet</t></si><si><t>The name of the worksheet in the Measurement Values spreadsheet that contains the reported measurement data for different water rights</t></si><si><t>Is "QAQC_MEASUREMENT_VALUES_SPREADSHEET_PATH" a SharePoint path?</t></si><si><t>Path to the manually reviewed Median-Based Unit Conversion Errors spreadsheet</t></si><si><t>Leave this blank if the manual review has not yet been completed. Otherwise, specify a path to the manually reviewed QAQC spreadsheet here. (This spreadsheet should be the file that was output by "Expected_Demand_Units_Issue_Flagger.R")</t></si><si><t>Name of the review worksheet in the Median-Based Unit Conversion Errors spreadsheet</t></si><si><t>The name of the worksheet in the Median-Based Unit Conversion Errors spreadsheet that contains the manual review table</t></si><si><t>Is "QAQC_MEDIAN_BASED_UNIT_CONVERSION_ERRORS_SPREADSHEET_PATH" a SharePoint path?</t></si><si><t>Path to the manually reviewed Duplicate Reporting spreadsheet</t></si><si><t>Leave this blank if the manual review has not yet been completed. Otherwise, specify a path to the manually reviewed QAQC spreadsheet here. (This spreadsheet should be the file that was output by "Multiple_Owner_Analysis.R")</t></si><si><t>Name of the review worksheet in the Duplicate Reporting spreadsheet</t></si><si><t>The name of the worksheet in the Duplicate Reporting spreadsheet that contains the manual review table</t></si><si><t>Is "QAQC_DUPLICATE_REPORTING_SPREADSHEET_PATH" a SharePoint path?</t></si><si><t>Path to the manual review Empty Reports spreadsheet</t></si><si><t>This path leads to a spreadsheet containing the results of a manual review for empty reports. (This spreadsheet is produced by "Check_Empty_Reports.R")</t></si><si><t>Name of the review worksheet in the Empty Reports spreadsheet</t></si><si><t>The name of the worksheet in the Empty Reports spreadsheet that contains the manual review table and results</t></si><si><t>Is "NA_REPORTS_SPREADSHEET_PATH" a SharePoint path?</t></si><si><t>Path to the spreadsheet that contains PODs and their coordinates</t></si><si><t>The path to a spreadsheet that contains "APPLICATION_NUMBER", "POD_ID", "LATITUDE", and "LONGITUDE" columns for each POD</t></si><si><t>Name of the worksheet in the POD coordinates spreadsheet</t></si><si><t>The name of the worksheet in the POD coordinates spreadsheet that contains the latitude and longitude data</t></si><si><t>Is "POD_COORDINATES_SPREADSHEET_PATH" a SharePoint path?</t></si><si><t>The coordinate reference system for the POD coordinates spreadsheet</t></si><si><t>The coordinate/projection system used for the latitude and longitude data specified in the POD coordinates spreadsheet (This entry should be written in a format acceptable by the "sf" package's functions, like "NAD83" or "epsg:4326")</t></si><si><t>Path to the GIS file that contains a layer of the different watershed sub-divisions</t></si><si><t>To assign PODs to different watershed sub-divisions, the script requires a layer containing separate polygons for each sub-division.</t></si><si><t>The watershed sub-divisions' layer name</t></si><si><t>If "SUBBASIN_POLYGONS_DATABASE_PATH" leads to a geodatabase or similar GIS structure, specify the sub-divisions' layer name here. Otherwise, leave it blank.</t></si><si><t>Is "SUBBASIN_POLYGONS_DATABASE_PATH" a SharePoint path?</t></si><si><t>The name(s) of the field(s) in the subbasin layer that identify different subbasins</t></si><si><t>The subbasin GIS layer should have a field (or group of fields) that uniquely identifies each subbasin. The field name(s) should be specified here. If there is more than one field required, they should be separated by a semicolon. (All field names specified in this column will be appended to the POD dataset during the subbasin assignment phase.)

The field name (or first field name) specified in this column should be the same field that distinguishes sub-basins in the connectivity matrix.</t></si><si><t>Path to the spreadsheet that contains the sub-basin connectivity matrix</t></si><si><t>The path to a spreadsheet that contains the connectivity matrix for the sub-basins. The identifying sub-basin names should be the first field name mentioned in "SUBBASIN_FIELD_ID_NAMES".</t></si><si><t>The name of the worksheet in the connectivity matrix spreadsheet</t></si><si><t>The name of the worksheet in the connectivity matrix spreadsheet that contains the matrix (0s and 1s with the sub-basin IDs as the row and column names)</t></si><si><t>Is "CONNECTIVITY_MATRIX_SPREADSHEET_PATH" a SharePoint path?</t></si><si><t>Path to the spreadsheet that contains manually assigned sub-basins for rights with PODs in more than one sub-basin</t></si><si><t>The path to a spreadsheet that contains values for each field in "SUBBASIN_FIELD_ID_NAMES" for each flagged water right</t></si><si><t>Name of the worksheet in the sub-basin manual assignment spreadsheet</t></si><si><t>The name of the worksheet in the sub-basin manual assignment spreadsheet that contains sub-basin data for each flagged "APPLICATION_NUMBER"</t></si><si><t>Is "SUBBASIN_MANUAL_ASSIGNMENT_SPREADSHEET_PATH" a SharePoint path?</t></si><si><t>EXCLUDED_REPORTING_YEARS</t></si><si><t>2021;2022</t></si><si><t>EXAMPLE/Russian River.gdb</t></si><si><t>InputData/Navarro_River_Watershed.gpkg</t></si><si><t>OutputData/NV_GIS_Preprocessing.xlsx</t></si><si><t>InputData/Reports</t></si><si><t>RR_pod_points_Merge_filtered_PA_2023-09-19.xlsx</t></si><si><t>Example_Path\NV_POD_StreamStats_Review.xlsx</t></si><si><t>Sheet_1</t></si><si><t>RR_Expected_Demand_Units_QAQC.xlsx</t></si><si><t>RR_Expected_Demand_Units_QAQC_Measurement_Values.xlsx</t></si><si><t>RR_Expected_Demand_Units_QAQC_Median_Based.xlsx</t></si><si><t>RR_Duplicate_Reports_Manual_Review.xlsx</t></si><si><t>RR_Empty_Reports_Manual_Review.xlsx</t></si><si><t>RR_Missing_MainStem_GIS_Manual_Assignment.xlsx</t></si><si><t>Required for "POD_StreamStats_Analysis.R". The script uses a single point to represent the exit location of the watershed's main tributary. The watershed boundary layer is required to identify this exit point. (Please consult the documentation for more information)</t></si></sst>